This is Trigun.
guitar solo
H-h-hah...
H-h-hah... Well?
Aren't you gonna shoot me?
Where do I find your boss?
I was bought.
It wasn't my fault.
The man I thought to be my father turned
out to be nothing more than an angel.
I don't know anything else, I swear.
Hey, it's dangerous to be too trusting.
What if I decided to get up
and shoot you in the back?
I'm not that trusting.
I kept my finger on the
trigger the whole time.
What now, Vash?
Routine report, date July Thou.
Two days after the incident
caused by a man named Monev,
tension still runs high in the city.
The events that occurred there made
me realize something all over again.
It's an awareness which becomes obscured
as I keep regular contact with him.
That being the reason Vash the Stampede
is called the Humanoid Typhoon.
I still don't understand.
Why is it that so much trouble
falls into this man's lap?
Last December,
four months ago, we, Meryl
Stryfe and Millie Thompson,
employees of the Bernardelli
Insurance Society main office,
were handed down our orders.
Our objective was to make
contact with Vash the Stampede,
a man wanted for 60 billion double dollars
under suspicion of
Class G property damage.
Upon locating this humanoid typhoon,
it was our mission to minimize any
trouble involving him and bring a quick
resolution to situations that had
already started what about bash and why?
Are you asking?
Don't tell me you two
innocent looking things
are after that 60 billion
double dollar reward?
Oh, not at all.
Yeah, actually we're just
passing through here on business!
Business?
Well, I didn't exactly see him myself.
As far as I could tell, he was
gone from the city by dawn.
Last I heard, he was
headed out to the east.
Can you tell me any more about him?
Hmm, well,
he stands about 12 fields tall,
and he wields a huge weapon,
he's supposed to have a
mohawk, and nerves of steel.
Apparently, he's got tons of henchmen,
and a reputation as the worst
womanizer anyone's ever seen.
Womanizer?
I heard what he said.
Huge weapon and a mohawk.
That's our man, alright.
Having obtained information of
someone matching Vash's description,
we finally achieved contact
with him after three months.
Now, what do you want?
I'm very pleased to meet you.
My name is Meryl.
I...
I'm Meryl Stryfe, and I'm here representing
the Bernardelli Insurance Society.
And I'm Millie Thompson!
This, uh, is a small
token of our goodwill.
Nice going, Meryl!
What are you doing?
Are you here with him?
It was him.
The outlaw, Vash the Stampede.
That's a lot different from
what actually happened.
I took a little bit of license
to keep it interesting.
Come on, Millie, do you want to
get a promotion or don't you?
At first glance, I must admit, it was
a bit difficult to tell if it was him.
This was because he didn't
act anything like the
legendary gunman that
I've heard so much about.
In fact, the only thing legendary
about him was his huge appetite.
Okay, then, what?
Stop!
Just not!
No! Dang it!
Disgusting.
Just ignore them.
Hey, insurance girls! Snail, wait!
Hey, where are you going?
I need your help!
How can you just leave me like this?
How about a little make-up kiss, brother?
He seemed to be nothing but a
vulgar, hopeless troublemaker.
And even worse yet, his incorrigible
lechery made him an exasperating idiot.
You can definitely count on me, Mr.
Cliff.
I don't let anyone in my sights get away,
and I'm known for my bullets
never missing their mark.
especially if it's the
heart of a beautiful lady.
Bang!
Meryl, are you okay?
Uh?
Just remembering what happened
that day gives me chest pains.
I feel like my heart's
going to burst a vessel.
I thought Vash was really funny back then.
I laughed all the time.
What are you talking about?
He wasn't funny.
He was downright weird.
Millie, nobody in their right mind
could tell that goofball was him.
How could you even think that?
But I thought it was him from the start.
You're the one who refused to believe it.
Does it bother you that much
that I could be right about him?
Millie, have you finished
writing the papers yet?
No, but I'll keep at it.
He tried to fool us with his perfect
portrayal of a good-for-nothing,
dim-witted loser,
but it soon became clear to me that his
antics were merely part of his little game.
I was able to confirm his
true identity as I watched
him resolve every incident
he was involved in.
Suicide?
To tell you the truth, I disapprove
of suicide more than anything.
All right, the boomerang it is.
What?
Dangerous toys are fun,
but you could get hurt.
You bastard!
Watch out!
Scary!
Sam!
Just no skill.
What the hell are you, anyway?
I'm your bodyguard and ace
gunman, just as advertised.
What do you think you're doing?
Trying to play the hero,
cowboy? No, not really.
I'm not as great as you might think I am.
Ah gee that's too bad
you've got a flat tire
well I guess you won't
be escaping in this!
Are you crazy do you have any idea what
you're getting yourself into Mister?
This gentleman here is the one and
only infamous humanoid typhoon!
He's Vash the Stampede!
That's funny.
Pardon me.
But I was under the impression
that he was a lot more handsome.
Are you implying that I
am not Vash the Stampede?
Maybe we should find out.
He was a superb gunman,
just as the rumors claimed,
and every incident he
was in was swiftly...
swiftly...
He did it so haphazardly.
How could those incidents have been
anything but dumb luck any of them
Still
Still it is the unmistakable truth that he
solved each incident
without the use of his gun.
He absolutely refused to harm
anyone even when citizens?
tried to kill him to collect
the bounty of his head.
Ah!
Can this be the end?
There he is! In here! Oh, crap!
I killed you!
I killed you now!
Oh, really? Do you mean me?
Momma!
Why does this keep happening to me?
I haven't done anything wrong,
but I'm always in trouble and
everybody's always picking on me.
What do I do, Momma?
Why am I crying in French?
Why does he act the way he does?
I can only speculate, but
perhaps part of the reason?
Can be found in the testimony
of Miss Monica Allen.
at the left of the city.
Only one person has to
die to save this city.
So please, Mr.
Vash, give yourself up.
Please don't move.
I understand your situation
better than you know.
However...
No, please, sir, don't do that.
Until I see this man you're after,
I have no choice but to keep moving.
Now, please.
Who do you think Mr.
Vash was referring to when he
mentioned the man Monica was after?
And so he finally took
his gun into his hand.
He pulled the trigger
for the first time to
save the very people who
had tried to kill him.
Hey, time's up, Wonderboy!
Throw the fear of death
into him, Goofstuff!
How did you do that?
I can't believe you both
are still alive and well!
I was kinda hoping you'd ditch
the woman and save your own skin!
Vash wouldn't do that!
He isn't that kind of person!
So you won't kill no matter what, huh?
You are disgusting!
You know what, Vess?
You're nothing but a damn hypocrite.
There's no way you haven't had to kill
troublemakers somewhere along the line.
How do I know?
Because nobody can survive what you've
been through without hurting somebody.
The $60 billion double dollar bounty
on your head is proof of that.
Well, what do you have to say
for yourself, Vestas Stampede?
You're finally ready to fight, are you?
Oh, so you want to draw?
You felt it, twice!
Already, even your puny brain can realize
my son's fist is a force to be reckoned.
or do you really believe
you'll survive another one?
This is your last chance to run!
Although no matter how fast you are,
within the next few minutes
you'll be smashing to tiny pieces!
Now pay attention,
because as a courtesy I'm going to lecture
you on just what a stupid
fool you really are!
Using this technique!
A human mincemeat special course!
Don't have to quit!
Enjoy being a hero for a moment,
They've died in a most humiliating way.
He did it!
It changed course!
That was great!
It cost my son's fist to be off
course with six little bullets!
Not quite, Doc.
I have one left.
Could be my special one.
I can't believe it did
you see what he did you
really beat him and he did
it with only six bullets,
unbelievable!
Suddenly it's become very clear to me
why he is called the Humanoid Typhoon.
It's actually him, he's for real,
the legendary outlaw, Vash the Stampede.
Oh yeah, no matter what, I think
this man is Vash the Stampede.
Love and peace!
Love and peace! Love and peace!
You're really fun to watch.
Vash the Stampede.
Every time I observe his actions,
I can't help but sense something
hidden deep within him.
Something we can't begin to understand.
but this much is certain
everyone who has become involved
with him has somehow regained
an emotion which was once lost.
Father!
Father, I'm coming!
I'm...
I'm all right, honey.
This can't be happening.
It was you all the time.
Like I've mentioned so many times before,
nothing beats Hardwon fame.
From this point on, we're gonna go
on living without relying on anyone.
It'll be just the two of us.
That's nice of you guys to say that.
But I still wonder...
Mr. Vash!
Stay back!
Stay away from me.
Who is he?
That's not Vash.
That is not the same man.
Who is that man?
Can he possibly be the
real Vash the Stampede?
The evil 60 billion double dollar outlaw
with the fire of hell burning in his eyes?
You will pay, you will pay for this.
They're dead.
People are dead.
Who the hell cares?
You killed all the people!
They're all dead, and you killed them all!
And you were the one solely responsible!
Now it is your turn to die!
There are so many sides to him.
Which is the real Vash?
I don't understand.
Listen.
We're all scared.
We can't sleep at night.
You're not the only one.
Can't we get someone to tell
him to get out of this hotel?
Don't bash the stampede to get out?
Are you insane?
Bash, are you all right?
So those scars are the price you paid for
dealing with your opponents
without killing them.
It's not exactly something
I like girls to see.
I think many of them would run away.
I wouldn't run away.
What I mean is they wouldn't run away.
Uh, Vash, I've been meaning to
ask you this for a while now.
You haven't done anything wrong,
yet terrible things keep
happening to you all the time.
The townspeople look at you like
you're some sort of criminal.
Doesn't that bother you?
How can you go on living this way?
It seems so awful.
I can't.
I can't do that.
I haven't yet buried my past.
There's no way I can live in peace?
Until I've come to terms with it.
and I'm able to finally put it behind me.
You leaving?
Hey, thanks, Sheriff, for
letting me go like this.
I'm only doing it because I
don't want you in my town.
And I don't want you.
Thanks.
I just want you to get the hell out.
Yeah.
I guess I Will do you plan
to follow him this time?
Course. I am. I have to.
It's my job. That's True.
You're right.
I can't very well leave the
two of you alone together.
So I Suppose I better come along.
Anyone ever tell you you're
just simply annoying?
Oh Oh really?
Young lady.
When you travel all alone in the
desert it can be very perilous.
But if you act now you can hire your
very own bodyguard free of charge.
And my work is guaranteed.
Oh? Great.
I take my eyes off him for a
minute and he's at it again.
Wait.
Where are you going?
Hey?
Don't just walk away.
Come on now.
Young lady.
Bash the stampede.
Thank
you so much
for
watching.
I'll just leave my left.
When I'm looking at my eyes
and I'm looking at my eyes!
I don't need anything else.
Yeah?
If you only face forward, there
is something you will miss seeing.
It is a virtue to devote oneself to something,
firmly believing in one's own ideals.
But that does not mean it's alright to
belittle the ideals or feelings of others.
If you lead such a busy life, and you
don't realize how your parents feel,
it's only self-satisfaction it's all
right to stop every now and again
if you want a moment's rest if you
want to feel what other people feel